

Magdalena Mishkov

UX/UI Designer

https://mishkovm.github.io/portfolio/

Paderborn, Germany+491781861567magdalena.mishkov@gmail.com

About

I am a designer with experience in **UX/UI**, **graphic**, and **web** design. The seven years in the banking field provided me with solid **analytical** and **organisational** skills, as well as ability to understand people and find the best solution for their problems. Today I use those key skills to create **inclusive digital solutions** through research and empathy. I aspire to WOW users with a "**how didn't they come up with this before?**" type of impression.

Education

UX Gym Training, Bonanza Studios, 01/2024 - present

UX/UI Design Certification, Brainster, 06/2021 - 06/2022

Master of Science (MSc), Monetary economics, finances and banking, Faculty of Economics, University Ss. Cyril and Methodius, 10/2013 - 09/2018

Bachelor of Science (BSc), Financial Management,

Faculty of Economics, University Ss. Cyril and Methodius, 10/2009 - 10/2013

Work experience

Designer, Homebase Real Estate GmbH, Berlin, 06/2024 - present

- creating strong brand identity to our clients
- preparing online and offline set of creatives
- building landing pages from scratch to final hand-off
- strategic planning and designing visual appealing creatives for Social media campaigns

Self-employed UI/UX Designer, 03/2024 - present

providing design and development services to a broad range of freelance clients

Junior Designer, allmyhomes GmbH, Berlin, 04/2023 - 10/2023

- creating and implementing user-centered interfaces through data-driven analysis; building landing pages from concept to final hand-off
- improving the user experience by continuous testing
- implementing responsive design, resulting in improved mobile user experience
- strategic planning and designing visual appealing creatives for Social media campaigns
- collaborating with Branding, Performance marketing and Project managers to ensure deliverables are aligned with the client's vision cross-functional collaboration

Design Intern, allmyhomes GmbH, Berlin, 10/2022 - 03/2023

supported graphic designers in their projects, which involved collecting **research**, creating advertisements material and **brainstorming alternative ideas** and realising them

Business Assistant of the MB, NLB Banka AD Skopje, Skopje, 07/2015 - 06/2019

provided comprehensive support to MB members, efficiently coordinating their daily activities, and facilitating smooth operations to **enhance productivity** and **maximise their effectiveness**

Bank Advisor, NLB Banka AD Skopje, Skopje, 01/2012 - 06/2015

successfully **identified customer needs** for both investment and lending, providing tailored financial solutions and expert advice that resulted in **increased customer engagement** and loyalty

Design skills

Competitive Analysis
User Research
User Persona
User Journey
Empathy Maps
User Flow
Information Architecture
Typography & Layout
Wireframing
Prototyping

Soft skills

Usability Testing

Visual Design Principles

User Interface Design

Creative thinking
Empathy
Problem-solving
Quick learning
Collaboration
Adaptability
Time management
Curiosity
Can-do attitude

Toolkit

Figma
Adobe Creative Suite
(Photoshop, Illustrator,
InDesign)
Miro
Unbounce
Wordpress
Visual Studio
GitHub

Languages

Macedonian - Native English - Business German - Intermediate French - Elementary